[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
Just like that,
the end of summer quietly slipped away.
Time flew by.
And we welcomed the inevitable,
highly anticipated day
for Korean high schoolers.
Today is the day
of the college entrance exam.
The whole country is freezing cold.
[10 degrees lower than usual...
The worst cold wave in CSAT history hits]
10 degrees lower than this time
in previous years—
the worst cold wave
in CSAT history has hit.
Seoul's morning temperature dropped
to minus 8 degrees.
This is for Cha Dohyun.
Tell him not to be nervous.
All the best.
And we,
who thought would stay
in that time forever...
Hey, the meat is burning. Flip it!
Unknowingly got ready to become adults.
This time it's your fault.
Come on, cheers! Cheers!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Now we are 20 years old.
A man's life...
-Starts now!
Come on! Have more meat.
-Thank you!
Okay.
Sir,
I want a drink.
Go get it yourself.
Okay!
Hey, what do you want to do
after graduation?
Me?
I want to be a rapper, sir.
A rapper?
That's cool.
You punk.
That kind of drink...
I should be the one pouring them for you.
Come sit down.
Thank you.
Oh my, you brats
have all grown up so quickly.
Come on, let me pour you a glass.
Thank you!
No problem.
Here, let me pour you one.
Thank you!
All right.
Hey, what are you guys planning to do
in the future?
I want to be a congressman.
You're more suited to be the president
than a congressman.
Right? Right?
But someone told me
not to be the president.
Who?
Our teacher!
He probably doesn't like me.
Our teacher...
does dislike you.
He does.
Damn it. What are you going to do
in the future?
He'll probably going to be a rapper.
Things will work out somehow.
He's always so laid-back.
What are you expecting?
As for him...
Forget it.
What about you?
He just has to take over this place.
Damn, I'm so jealous.
I want to be Eunho's underling
instead of the president.
Me too, me too!
Damn it.
Me too.
I don't know what to do either.
Cheers!
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
-Cheers!
Damn you, Cha Dohyun!
you haven't drunk a drop, right?
Have a glass!
Just drink this.
No.
Then get out.
I...
I'll corrupt him sooner or later.
You're gonna corrupt him?
Hey, Cha Dohyun is already...
Oh man,
closing on a busy day like today...
Are you eating well?
-Yes.
Yes, sir!
Wait, why is he so excited?
Why is his face so red?
Oh,
he's just hot from grilling the meat.
He did all the grilling?
I've been grilling the whole time.
I want another bottle of—
Hey,
you guys are still 19.
Not for long, ma'am.
In 10 minutes,
we'll be adults.
It's almost time.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wow, so many people.
Yeah.
[At the scene of Boksingak 2026 Countdown]
Shall we go over there too?
Yeo Eunho.
Let's go.
Where to?
Hey, where are you going?
Aren't we counting down together?
Where are you going?
Drink.
So annoying.
Hey!
You should at least tell me
where we're going.
We've got to hurry up.
Before it's too late.
What are you doing?
Three, two, one.
Hello, 20-year-old Yeo Eunho.
You're too impatient.
Impatient?
I've held back a long time for this day.
Relax.
I told you to relax.
You should've given me time to relax.
By the way, are you going out?
Get dressed.
We're going out.
It's the middle of the night.
Where are we going?
You'll see when we get there.
But I'm tired.
Yeo Eunho.
Come here.
What's going on? Is the sun not up yet?
Make a wish.
I hope I never fight with Yeo Eunho,
and we stay happy forever.
How many times have I told you
to make a wish in your heart, silly?
It won't come true if you say it out loud.
No.
My wish
will come true.
[Sung Inho]
[Kim Domin]
[Summertime]
Why are we
suddenly wearing school uniforms?
There aren't many days left
for us to wear school uniforms.
Let's go on a date.
Thanks.
Do you want a sip?
Sure.
Crazy.
It's good.
Peace.
So pretty.
Yeah.
Hey, you can't do that—
I would like to offer my
congratulations to all of you
[Congratulations on your graduation]
who are about to enter society.
-I sincerely wish...
-Jaewon.
-for you to go through every season in peace.
-Let's go to the internet cafe.
Didn't the homeroom teacher say
we're celebrating today?
-For your brand new start...
-Why go there?
Said he'd buy us drinks.
I'll be cheering you on.
Thank you.
Then let's go to the internet cafe
after this.
Okay.
Finally, please welcome the valedictorian
for the graduation speech.
It's Cha Dohyun.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Cha Dohyun, speaking on behalf
of the graduates.
Before we knew it,
we've spent 3 summers
and winters here.
Right now, both happy memories
and difficult times come to mind.
In this not-so-short time,
we've learned a lot.
Patience and resilience,
friendship and jealousy,
hatred and love, and so on.
That summer of ours
that once felt so unfamiliar
yet passionate which seemed
like it would never end
have passed by without you knowing.
And we don't know how cold and ruthless
the society we're about to enter will be.
Perhaps we will lose our way and wander.
Perhaps the day will come
when we drift apart.
But...
please don't forget that
after winter comes spring,
and summer will eventually arrive again.
Please don't waste time
blaming and regretting the past.
Instead, welcome
the new times ahead with a smile.
Whichever path you take,
I sincerely hope your winter
won't be too long.
Congratulations on your graduation.
One, two, three.
Oh, I blinked.
One more.
I'm not going to take anymore.
-Take it quickly.
-Hurry up.
Hurry up, do a quick one.
Hurry.
One, two, three.
Done.
I heard you got into Hankuk University!
Congratulations.
Thanks.
This is my son.
Is that so?
Thank you.
Thanks.
Keep in touch.
Hey, you guys take a picture.
Yeah.
What for?
Come on, hurry up.
Gosh.
Get closer.
Look closer. That's right.
Smile!
Smile.
I'm leaving right now.
Okay.
You're here.
Sorry.
I wanted to come earlier,
but a group of customers came in.
Have you been waiting long?
Not really.
Oh,
my mom told me to give this to you.
She really didn't have to.
Just take it.
Mind if I smoke?
Go ahead.
It's your front door anyway.
Hey, Kwon Yihyun,
the smoke in the club
must be suffocating too.
Aren't you sick of it?
How's helping out at the restaurant?
It sucks.
Three minutes in front of the grill
and I'm drenched in sweat.
The aircon doesn't even help either.
I never knew people loved BBQ this much.
I thought it'd be
a whole new world after graduation.
Turns out it's not.
I actually think
being in school was better.
Oh,
Yoo Wonho started learning welding
through his dad's connection.
Everyone is busy going to college
or finding a job.
I'm the only one
who doesn't know what to do.
Take your time.
What?
You can be calm
because you have backup.
Kwon Yihyun,
are you going to keep working at the club?
Hard to say.
Even as a waiter,
it must be dangerous, right?
It's fine.
Not too bad.
True.
You can definitely handle it.
What about Cha Dohyun?
What?
I mean, is he doing well?
We broke up.
[Summertime]
Who is he? Someone you know?
Yeah,
he's my favorite person in the world.
What the heck?
Cha Dohyun,
you have someone like that too?
Wow, it's Yeo Eunho.
Hello.
I'm a friend of Dohyun
in the same department.
Yeah, I've been too busy. Sorry.
Damn it, are you happy now?
It's all my fault, okay?
I'm sorry.
Selfish jerk.